Ta-ra-ra, ta-ra-ra
Ta-ra-ra-raaa
What if we choose each other?
Ta-ra-ra, ta-ra-ra
Tell me
if you believe in messages from dreams
If you believe in coincidence
or that everything has its time
What do you know
of the language of the stars?
The one they use in silence
with which they've told a thousand stories
through the ages
Does chance decide our destiny
or do we choose it?
Did someone already choose the road
or do we build it?
Maybe the answers
aren't meant to be found
Maybe it's choosing
who to invent them with
Why be spectators
if we can be actors?
Choose to watch life passing by
or take your hand
and change the perspective
WHAT IF WE CHOOSE EACH OTHER?
We choose each other
We invent a brand-new destiny
WHOLE NEW WORLDS
We are the architects
of a brand-new road
WHAT IF WE CHOOSE EACH OTHER?
We choose each other
Ta-ra-ra, ta-ra-ra
Ta-ra-ra-raaa
We choose each other
Talk to me
about the language of dreams
And building whole new worlds
What if we create new cities?
What if we travel through time?
Travel through other realities
and build our own empire
If you go to Mars
I'll stay home and walk the dog
WHAT IF WE CHOOSE EACH OTHER?
We choose each other
We invent a brand-new destiny
WHOLE NEW WORLDS
We are the architects
of a brand-new road
WHAT IF WE CHOOSE EACH OTHER?
We choose each other
You imagine it
and I will build it
I will build it
You imagine it
Ta-ra-ra, ta-ra-ra
If that world doesn't exist
We'll invent it together
If the story that is written
is ours to decide
And if every day
we discover each other again
You imagine it
I will build it
You choose me
I choose you
WHAT IF WE CHOOSE EACH OTHER?
WE CHOOSE EACH OTHER!
We invent a brand-new destiny
WHOLE NEW WORLDS
We are the architects
of a brand-new road
WHAT IF WE CHOOSE EACH OTHER?
WE CHOOSE EACH OTHER!
You imagine it
and I will build it
WHAT IF WE CHOOSE EACH OTHER?
WE CHOOSE EACH OTHER!
Ta-ra-ra, ta-ra-ra
If that world doesn't exist
We'll invent it together
Ta-ra-ra
What if we choose each other?